Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Addition, 1901-2017 and undated; 1
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1951-2013 and undated; 14
    - OAAA--Rap/Matrix/Hall of Fame, 2003 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-084)
      Rap open and coffee break; Rap credits; Matrix open and coffee break; OBIE judge video; McDonald's Hall of Fame HIRE; McDonald's Hall of Fame NO HIRE
    - OAAA--Reflections final cut; 4:12, 1999 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-085)
    - OAAA--Regional sales video, Slam Dunk '98, 1998 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-086)
    - OAAA--Regional sales video, Slam Dunk '98, 1998 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-087)
    - OAAA--Sales video and OBIE finalists continuous play dub, 1993 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-088)
    - OAAA--Scenic America: Signs, Signs, The Economic and Environmental Benefits of Community Sign Control, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-089)
    - OBIE Awards--64th annual OBIE Awards, 2006 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-090)
    - OBIE Awards--64th annual OBIE Awards, 2006 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-091)
    - OBIE Awards, 1984 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-092)
    - OBIE Awards dinner, 2004 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-093)
    - OBIE Awards--Best of Show images, undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-094)
    - OBIE Awards--Chevrolet Hall of Fame Winner; 2:09, 2001 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-095)
    - OBIE Awards--Devlinhair Productions, 1995 Obie/OAAA final version (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-096)
    - OBIE Awards--Finalists; 5:55, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-097)
    - OBIE Awards--Finalists/Bill Weithas presentation; Media's Medium; 19:35, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-098)
    - OBIE Awards--Hall of Fame/Obie Awards/Best of Show; 13:29, 2004 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-099)
    - OBIE Awards--Hall of Fame video; 2:10, 2000 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-100)
    - OBIE Awards--Judges Speak Out, 2001 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-101)
    - OBIE Awards--Judges Video/Winners/Hall of Fame/String Out, 2006 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-102)
    - OBIE Awards--Judging video; 4:00, 1999 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-103)
    - OBIE Awards--Judging video; 4:00, 1999 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-104)
    - OBIE Awards--Meryl Moskowitz; Judges: Obie version; 2:34, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-105)
    - OBIE Awards--Multi image xfer, 1994 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-106)
    - OBIE Awards--Obie Awards reprise; 3:25, 2000 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-107)
    - Outdoor Advertising Association of Michigan--Partners in the Community; 10:40, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-108)
    - Outdoor Works marketing video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-109)
    - Pacific Outdoor--Permanent Bulletin video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-110)
    - Pacific Outdoor--Posting video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-111)
    - Pacific Outdoor--Real Estate video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-112)
    - Pacific Outdoor--Rotary video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-113)
    - Pacific Outdoor--Trade video, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-114)
    - Peter Max, CNN Morning News; 7:00, 1997 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-115)
    - Politically Incorrect, ABC: mention of billboards in Baltimore, 1997 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-116)
    - Postar (UK)--The Research Process, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-117)
    - Prime Time Live--Old billboards, scenic byways, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-118)
    - Profile Systems--Problems, Solutions; 6:21, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-119)
    - PosterVision--Bernstein Masterwork; 19:16, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-120)
    - PowerVision--We've got the Power! 3:00, 1998 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-121)
    - R.C. Maxwell--100 Years of Outdoor 1894-1994 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-122)
    - Rashawn Capers AMW Show, 2005 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-123)
    - Roger Kemp segment; 3:02, undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-124)
    - Ron Jon testimonials, 1995 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-125)
    - Shelter Advertising Sells, Gary Crawford, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-126)
    - Sunday Morning--The Great White Way, 1992 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-127)
    - Super Boards; 4:00, 1993 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-128)
    - U.S. Senate--Floor debate, Highway Bill, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-129)
    - U.S. Senate--Floor debate, Mikulski, Reid Amendment; 2:14:00, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-130)
    - U.S. Senate--Debate on Stafford Amendment, 1987 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-131)
    - Van Wagner--Times Square USA; 5:54, undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-132)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--AAA Foundation, C-Span; 39:25, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-133)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Adoption/Billboard, ABC Good Morning America; 4:18, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-134)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Advertising/Tivo, PBS Nightly Business Report, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-135)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Are Highway Billboards Necessary? FNC The Edge with Paula Zahn; 7:55. Should Billboards Be Banned for Beauty? Fox News Live; 3:23, 2000 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-136)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboard/Murder, WRC News 4 at 6; :36, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-137)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboard: Looking for a Killer, WRC News 4 at 5; 3:28, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-138)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboard: Looking for a Killer, WRC News 4 at 6; 3:28, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-139)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboard Advertising, NBC Face to Face; 28:21, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-140)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboard Advertising, ABC Good Morning America; 5:25, 1996 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-141)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboards, Fox America's Most Wanted; 6:38, 2005 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-142)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Billboards, CNN Larry King Live; 1:02, 2002 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-143)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Books about BS, CBS 60 Minutes; 13:42, 2005 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-144)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Bus Billboard Advertising, PBS Nightly Business Report; 2:15, 1997 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-145)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Explicit Billboards, CBS Early Show; 3:54, 2004 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-146)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--FBI Billboard, WRC News 4; 3:25, 2004 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-147)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Free OJ Billboard, CNN Early Prime; :28, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-148)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Gannett Billboards/Burt Kemp, CBS This Morning; 1:55, 1991 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-149)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Gary, Indiana/Murder Capital of U.S., CNN Morning News; :26, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-150)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Highway Beautification/Laura Bush, CNN Larry King Live; :49, 2001 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-151)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--IG Nobel Prize, CBS Sunday Morning; 9:00, 2003 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-152)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Kevin Reilly/Lamos Advertising, CNBC Squawk Box; 4:12. Gulf H.S./Joe Camel Billboard, NBC Today; 1:29, 1997 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-153)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--NAACP Billboard Advertising, WBAL 11 News; :47, 2004 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-154)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Outdoor Advertising Association, CNNFN The Flipside; 3:57, 2004 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-155)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Pass It On, ABC Good Morning America; 7:00, 2004 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-156)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--PETA Billboard, WRC News 4; :26, 2003 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-157)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Peter Max/Corey Williams Scholarship Fund, NBC Today; 7:18, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-158)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Roger Kemp, A Current Affair; 6:40, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-159)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Sub Base Billboard, Fox 61 News; :37, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-160)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Technology and Billboards; CNN World News; 2:45, 1994 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-161)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--The Cut, CBS; 1:30:00, 2005 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-162)
    - VMS (Video Monitoring Service)--Tobacco Ban, ABC News Channel 8; 2:29, 1997 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-163)
    - Wheels America Advertising Mobile Billboards, Atlanta Olympics and WBRE-TV News Coverage; 6:00, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-164)
    - Yesco: 75 Light Years 1920-1995 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-165)
    - ZipFlex--Whiteco Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL00963-VHS-166)
    - 53rd Annual Obie Awards, camera 1 tape 1; 60:00, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-001)
    - 53rd Annual Obie Awards, camera 1 tape 2; 60:00, 1995 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-002)
    - Digital Billboard Sources (OAAA), 2006 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-003)
    - Get to the Core (OAAA) animated graphic loop; 32:00, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-004)
    - OAAA single sheet 1, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-005)
    - OAAA single sheet 2, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-006)
    - OAAA single sheet 3, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-007)
    - OAAA tape 1, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-008)
    - OAAA tape 1, undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-009)
      Includes Two Guys in a Car; Talking Metro
    - OAAA tape 2, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-010)
    - OAAA tape 2, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-011)
    - OAAA tape 3, 2005 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-012)
    - OBIE judges Miami tape 1, green screen, 2008 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-013)
    - OBIE judges Miami tape 2, 2008 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-014)
    - OBIE judges Miami tape 3, 2008 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-015)
    - #3 Neil Kraft, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-016)
    - #4 Gerry Miller, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-017)
    - #5 Lee Lynch, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-018)
    - #6 Trace Hallowell, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-019)
    - #7 Fred Tio, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-020)
    - #8 Tony Angotti, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-021)
    - #9 Tony Angotti part 2, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-022)
    - Cracker Barrel: Nick Simulia, Director of Advertising, on Outdoor Advertising; :90, 2005 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-023)
    - Crispin Porter + Bogusky: MLB impact video, 2008 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-024)
    - Green Highways; 4:04, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-025)
    - Interview with Michael Tantala, Digital Billboards, tape 1 of 2, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-026)
    - Interview with Michael Tantala, Digital Billboards, tape 2 of 2, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-027)
    - Interview with Ronilee Small, Vegetation, tape 2 of 2, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-028)
    - McDonald's Hall of Fame: Hire; 1:46, 2003 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-029)
    - OAAA Best of Show Award--Animation; 30:00, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-030)
    - OAAA Billboards--Richmond, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-031)
    - OAAA--Building Billboards Beautifully; 10:10, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-032)
    - OAAA compilation, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-033)
      Includes: Commercials video; 2nd day video; Chairman; Chairman outtakes; Judges videos
    - OAAA day 2 open and coffee break, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-034)
    - OBIE--BBDO New York: Adam Kanzer (BBC), undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-035)
    - OBIE--BBDO New York: Bank of America, undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-036)
    - OBIE--BBDO Toronto; 1:11, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-037)
    - OBIE Awards--BBDO West; 1:44, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-038)
      Includes: Air New Zealand; San Francisco Zoo
    - OBIE--BBDO Detroit; Jeep Wrangler "Flyswatter Outdoor"/John O'Hea, 2007 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-039)
    - OAAA--Dr. Lewin interview, 2008 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-040)
    - OAAA--Flip Flops, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-041)
    - OAAA--Nancy Fletcher video letter to India, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-042)
    - OAAA/TAB Rap Studio #1, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-043)
    - OAAA/TAB--Steve, rap and matrix, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-044)
    - OAAA/TAB tape 4, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-045)
    - OAAA--The Martin Agency, 2006 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-046)
    - OAAA--Purex, Frank Detallo/Energy BBDO, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-047)
    - OAAA: Single sheet 4, disc 1a, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-048)
    - OAAA--reel 4 Interviews: Weill/Macavelli/Jackson, 2001 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-049)
    - OAAA-reel 5, 2001 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-050)
      Includes Obie awards; Hotel interior; Hotel exterior; POV intro room; Table shot; Times Square night; Lincoln Center night
    - OAAA Vegetation; Philadelphia/Jeff Kempter, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-051)
    - OAAA Vegetation and Digital Billboards, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-052)
    - OAAA Vegetation and Digital Billboards, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-053)
    - OAAA Vegetation B-roll, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-054)
    - OAAA Vegetation and Digital B-roll, Philadelphia, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-055)
    - OAAA--53rd Annual Obie Awards, camera 1 tape 2; 60:00, 1995 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-056)
    - OBIE--BBDO West, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-057)
      Includes: San Francisco Zoo "Boo at the Zoo"
    - OBIE--Carling "Taxi", 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-058)
    - OBIE--Judges, reel 1 part 1; 30:00, 1995 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-059)
    - OBIE--Judges, reel 1 part 2; 15:00, 1995 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-060)
    - OBIE--Dieste Harmel and Partners, Dallas; Mack Simpson, Christian Sendra, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-061)
    - OBIE--Disney award winner, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-062)
    - OBIE--EJE Sociedad Publicitaria (Buenos Aries, Argentina), Immodium billboard; 1:00, undated (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-063)
    - OBIE--FedEx Kinko's winner video, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-064)
    - OBIE--Friskies "Parakeets", 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-065)
    - OBIE--Lavoie and Postaer speeches, 2008 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-066)
    - OBIE--McDonald's "Sundial", Leo Burnett, 2007 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-067)
    - OBIE--Tape 1, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-068)
    - OBIE--Tape 2, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-069)
    - OBIE--Tape 2, 2003 (Box AV11, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-070)
    - OBIE Judges: Rich Gagnon, Jim Lesser, Joe Sciarrotta, 2007 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-071)
    - OBIE Judges: Jose Reyes, Bill Ludwig, Margaret Keene, Rich Gagnon, 2007 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-072)
    - OBIE Judges tape 4, 2008 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-073)
    - OBIE judges taping, tape 1, 2006 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-074)
    - OBIE judges taping, tape 2, 2006 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-075)
    - OBIE no spots, undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-076)
    - OBIE support--Pong, undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-077)
    - OBIE--Taxi, Covenant House, 2008 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-078)
    - OBIE--Awards video Paranormal State, 2008 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-079)
    - OBIE--Awards video Paranormal State, Sawtooth Group, PBR Video, 2008 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-080)
    - OBIE--Paul Lavoie Paddle, 2008 (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-081)
    - OAAA DV shots tape 4, undated (Box AV12, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-082)
    - OBIE--Shades of Green with UPS, The Martin Agency; 1:25, 2008 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-083)
    - OBIE--Toronto Humane Society, Leo Burnett, 2008 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-084)
    - OBIE--Winner video, Coke Zero "Inspirations", 2008 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-085)
    - OBIE--Winner video, BBC World and HBO, 2008 (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-086)
    - TM Advertising--Nationwide Insurance "Life Comes At You Fast", undated (Box AV13, Video-cassette RL00963-Bcam-087)
    - Clear Channel International--Case studies, Press Images (Jpeg, PPT, PPS), undated (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-001)
    - Eller Media--Los Angeles Yard Images (Jpeg), 2000-2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-002)
    - Get to the Core (OAAA)-Broadway Classics (CD), 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-003)
    - Digital Billboards (OAAA), 2007 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-004)
    - Facts About Outdoor Advertising (OAAA), undated (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-005)
    - Green Highways (OAAA), 2007 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-006)
    - OBIE Awards (tiff 72dpi), 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-007)
    - OBIE Awards, 2003 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-008)
    - OBIE Awards, 2004 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-009)
    - OBIE Awards, 2007 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-010)
    - OBIE Awards, 2008 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-011)
    - OBIE Awards, 2009 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-012)
    - OBIE Awards, 2010 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-013)
    - OBIE Awards, 2001 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-014)
    - OBIE Awards, 2012 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-015)
    - OBIE Awards, 2013 (Box AV13, Video-disc RL00963-OP-016)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--OAA Millennium Plan, speakers DeWitt Mallary, Cynthia Evans, Scott MacDuffie, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-001)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Speaker Brian O'Neill, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-002)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Speaker Elliott Young, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-003)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Speaker Erwin Ephron, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-004)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Speaker Roger Parry, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-005)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 1: International, Roger Parry, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-006)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 1: International, Roger Parry, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-007)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 2: Outdoor Creativity, Brian O'Neill, Goldberg Moser O'Neill, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-008)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 3: OAAA Eye Tracking, Elliott Young, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-009)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 4: The OAAA Creative Library/Outreach: The New Outdoor Reach and Frequency Model/Standards and Practices in Outdoor Media, R. DeWill Marrary (VMS), Cynthia Evans (Time), Scott MacDuffie (Zenith Media), 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-010)
    - Outdoor Day Seminar--Tape 5: Regency Theory, Ervin Ephron, 2000 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL00963-CS-011)
    - Man in Agency, undated (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL00963-MDV-001)
    - OBIE Awards video--BBDO West, San Francisco Zoo "Boo at the Zoo", 2008 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL00963-MDV-002)
    - OBIE--OAAA B-roll, 2005 (Box AV14, Video-cassette RL00963-MDV-003)
    - Advertising Club of Memphis--Advertising Stopped at 10:00 this Morning, 1952 (Box AV15, Audio-phonodisc RL00963-PD-001)
    - OAAA--Robert Vogler speech to Directors, 1951 (Box AV15, Audio-phonodisc RL00963-PD-002)
    - U.S. Treasury Department, U.S. Savings Bonds Division--U.S. Treasury Department Outdoor Advertising Committee Telephone Conference, 1951 (Box AV15, Audio-phonodisc RL00963-PD-003)
- Digital Materials, 1997-2019
  Conditions Governing Access
  Series contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - Presentation Materials, 2000-2007
    - Clear Channel International, 2000-2001; 24 still image and 17 document files; approx. 46MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0001)
    - Los Angeles Yard Images, 2001; 54 still image files; approx. 31MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0002)
    - Broadway Classics, 2001; 12 audio files; approx. 538MB (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0003)
    - Digital Bilboards, 2007; 5 video files; approx. 349MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0004)
    - Facts About Outdoor Advertising, 2005; 1 document files; approx. 49MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0005)
    - Green Highways, 2007; 5 video files; approx. 323MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0006)
    - OBIE Awards, 1997-2013; 2229 Still Image and 44 document files; approx. 2GB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001, Optical-disc RL00963-OP-0007 - RL00963-OP-0016)
      Missing 2002, 2005, and 2006
  - Published Materials, 2002-2019
    - Newsletters, 2001-2018; 646 document files; approx. 35.3MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001)
    - E-Newsclips, 2002-2004; 88 document files; approx. 12MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001)
    - Sales Tips, 2010-2019; 164 document files; approx. 5.4MB. (Digital-materials RL00963-SET-0001)